https://www.gtek.biz/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Written by Super User on 12 August 2020.
Posted in Uncategorised
Gtek 360 WiFi Mobile Application Privacy Policy
What is covered by this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) covers Gtek Communications' privacy and security policies for personal information collected by Gtek Communications in connection with the Gtek Communications Gtek 360 WiFi mobile application (the “App”). For this Privacy Policy, personal information refers to information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person with reference to a identifier, such as a name, an email address, an online identifier such as login credentials, or any other identifier by which that natural person may be contacted online or offline.
Gtek Communications understands the importance of privacy and security and is committed to providing a secure environment to protect the personal and private information provided by you in connection with your use of the App. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy sets out:
The personal information that is collected when you download, install, register for and/or use the App; and
Gtek Communications' practices associated with collecting, using, retaining, disclosing and protecting the information associated with your use of the App.
What is not covered by this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy DOES NOT apply to information:
Gtek Communications collects on its website; or
Gtek Communications may collect unrelated to Gtek Communications' provision of the App.
Information collected on Gtek Communications' website at www.gtek.biz is subject to Gtek Communications' privacy policy in the footer of the website pages (accessible at https://www.gtek.biz/privacy).
Personal information does not include information that has been anonymized or aggregated so that it can no longer be used to identify a specific natural person, whether in combination with other information or otherwise.
Privacy Policy applies for any use of the App
This Privacy Policy applies to Gtek Communications' policies and practices associated with the provision of the App described in the Gtek 360 WiFi Mobile Application End User License Agreement (the “Agreement”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand Gtek Communications' policies and practices regarding your information and how such information will be treated. If you do not agree with Gtek Communications' policies and practices, you should not install, use or access the App. By accepting and agreeing to the Agreement, or by using or accessing the App, you agree to this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. You should review this Privacy Policy periodically for updates and changes. Your continued use of the App after Gtek Communications revises this Privacy Policy means you accept those revisions.
Children Under the Age of 16
The App is not intended for children under 16 years of age, and Gtek Communications does not knowingly collect personal data of children under 16. If Gtek Communications learns that personal data from a child under 16 has been obtained or received without verification of parental consent, Gtek Communications will delete that information. If you believe Gtek Communications might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact Gtek Communications at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
How Gtek Communications Collects Your Information
Gtek Communications collects and processes information provided directly by you when you install the App and register for an account to use the App. Specifically, this information includes:
Your name, email address and location;
Browser information and session cookies related to your access and use of the App;
Data insights Gtek Communications attains based on correlation and analytics of your information collected in providing the App, which may be used in aggregated and dis-aggregated formats or to obtain trend analytics, to provide the App; and
Use of the above-described collected information in aggregated and dis-aggregated formats to enhance our current App or to provide App features.
How Gtek Communications Uses the Information
Gtek Communications uses the information collected as described in this Privacy Policy, including personal information, to:
Provide you with the App as described in the Agreement;
Implement, improve and/or enhance the App, including to make future releases available to you;
Carry out Gtek Communications' obligations as described or authorized in the Agreement and this Privacy Policy;
Enforce Gtek Communications' rights arising from the Agreement between you and Gtek Communications; and
Fulfill any other purpose authorized by you and reasonably required for the App.
Gtek Communications may also use the information collected as described in this Privacy Policy, including personal information, to inform you about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Gtek Communications does not contact you unless and only to the extent expressly authorized by you in writing.
Disclosure of Information
Gtek Communications does not sell or otherwise distribute or disclose your information to third parties other than as described or authorized in the Agreement, including this Privacy Policy.
Gtek Communications discloses the information to its subsidiaries, affiliates and certain third-party vendors and contractors that provide development, integration, web hosting and consulting services to Gtek Communications for the purpose of providing you with the App, to maintain, support, develop, improve and/or enhance the App and to fulfill Gtek Communications obligations associated with the App.
Gtek Communications may be required to disclose information under certain circumstances:
To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;
To enforce Gtek Communications' rights arising from the Agreement entered into between you and Gtek Communications;
If Gtek Communications believes disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Gtek Communications, its customers or other third parties; or
To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Gtek Communications' assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which you and/or you subscriber held by Gtek Communications are among the assets transferred.
Your Choices About Our Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Information
The provision of the information described in this Privacy Policy is necessary in order for you to use the App.
Your information is retained and used as described in this Privacy Policy. In the event you delete your account for the App in accordance with the terms of the Agreement, your information will be deleted within 30 days of the deletion of such account or within such other timeline as may be mandated by applicable law. You will no longer be able to access the App when your account is deleted.
You may set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If cookies are disabled or refused or if you block the use of other tracking technologies, some parts of the App may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
Accessing and Correcting Information
You can (a) access and review your information, including personal information, and (b) correct your information, by logging into the App and visiting the settings page.
Data Security
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Gtek Communications utilizes mechanisms such as intrusion detection systems, intrusion prevention systems, firewalls and encryption to secure information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.
Gtek Communications deploys Intrusion Detection Systems (IDS) and Intrusion Prevention Systems (IPS) to alert and proactively contain potential threats. Enhanced security visibility and coverage is enabled through added layers of firewall and IDS beyond the network perimeter. Management connections to servers are always authenticated and encrypted via Secure Shell (SSH) when administration access is required for troubleshooting, patch management, and upgrades.
Gtek Communications runs automated vulnerability scanning on all perimeter systems to identify potential security risks. Scanning applications are regularly updated to remain current and up to date on important security vulnerabilities. Patches are applied to all relevant systems, unless a compensating control is implemented.
Gtek Communications uses a variety of industry-standard security technologies and best practices to help protect information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. All data stored on the Gtek Communications systems is encrypted following industry standards using the strongest keys and ciphers. All communications with the App are protected with industry standard security protocols.
You control access to your account and, as set forth in the Agreement, you are obligated to keep your login credentials and passwords secure and protected and maintained as confidential. Although Gtek Communications implements measures that are reasonably designed to protect you, information may nevertheless be transmitted outside of Gtek Communications' systems. Any such transmission of information is at your own risk, and Gtek Communications is not responsible for any circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures provided.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Gtek Communications may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If Gtek Communications makes material changes to how Gtek Communications treats personal information under this Privacy Policy, Gtek Communications will notify you by email or other communication.
The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the end of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for ensuring Gtek Communications has an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you and for periodically visiting this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.
7/28/20
Contact Information
To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and Gtek Communications' privacy practices for the Cloud Services, contact Gtek Communications via e-mail at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Next
Products
GTEK Internet
GTEK Voice
Help Center
Make A Payment
FAQ
Coverage
Privacy Policy
Gtek Communications proudly provides Internet VOIP and Security services to these cities:
Alfred    Agua Dulce    Alice    Aransas Pass    Banquete    Bayside    Beeville    Ben Bolt    Benavides    Berclair    Bishop    Bluntzer    Calallen    Corpus Christi    Driscoll    Edroy    Falfurrias    George West    Goliad    Hallettsville    Holiday Beach     Ingleside    Kenedy    Kingsville    Mathis    Odem    Orange Grove    Palo Alto    Pettus    Port Aransas    Portland    Premont     Sandy Hollow    Odem    Orange Grove    Banquete    Refugio    Ricardo    Robstown    Rockport    Sandia    San Diego    Sinton    Skidmore    Swinney Switch    Taft    Three Rivers    Papalote    Victoria    Woodsboro
©
GTEK Communications. All Rights Reserved. Website Designed and Developed by Penguin Suits.
